Finding Aid for Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Organizational archives of CAAS 1962-2010
  - Persons, faculty 1962-2005
    - Diouf, Mamadou 2003 (Box 18)
    - Dykes, Jr., DeWitt 1988-1992 (Box 18)
    - Enyia, Dike Ogbuefi 1975-1979 (Box 18)
    - Enyia, Dike Ogbuefi, Syllabi 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Edie, Carlene J., Publications 1988, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Esonwanne, Uzoma 1990-1992 (Box 18)
    - Evans, Billy J. 1990 (Box 18)
    - Eyetsemition, Frank 1980-1990 (Box 18)
    - Farley, Reynolds 1986 (Box 18)
    - Fields, Barbara J. 1920-1990 (Box 18)
    - Flanagan, Brenda 1990 (Box 18)
    - Francis, Jacqueline 2003 (Box 18)
    - Gaines, Kevin 1990-2006 (Box 18)
    - Gish, Oscar 1979-1981 (Box 18)
    - Goduka, Ivy 1987 (Box 18)
    - Grovoqui, Siba 1990 (Box 18)
    - Hadjor, Kofi B. 1985-1987 (Box 18)
    - Hall, Jo Anne 1985-1994 (Box 18)
    - Hamer, Alice 1986 (Box 18)
    - Haniff, Nesha 1987-1990 (Box 18)
    - Hayden, Robert, Essays 1990 (Box 18)
    - Holl, Augustin 2007 (Box 18)
    - Holt, Thomas C. 1982-1991 (Box 18)
    - Holt, Thomas C., Publications 1982-1992, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Jackson, Charles A. 1990 (Box 19)
    - Jackson, James 1989-2003 (Box 19)
    - Jackson, Murray 1991 (Box 19)
    - Jessye, Eva A. 1976-1992 (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Lemuel 1986-2002 (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Lemuel, Publications 1969-2000, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Jones, Gayl 1975-1984 (Box 19)
    - Kelley, Robin 1991-1994 (Box 19)
    - Kelley, Robin, Publications 1984-1994, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Kolole, Omari, Publications 1984-1987 (Box 19)
    - Lawal, Babatunde 1990-1991 (Box 19)
    - Lawrence, Morris 1962-1980, 4 folders (Box 19)
      (photo in folder two)
    - Lewis, Earl 1989-1994 (Box 19)
    - Lewis, Earl, South Africa Project 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Lewis, Earl, Publications 1987-1996 (Box 19)
    - Lewis, Earl, "At Work and At Home" book MS 1988, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Omer, Afaf 1992 (Box 19)
    - Lindsay, Lisa 1997 (Box 19)
    - Lockard, Jon 1985-2007 (Box 20)
    - Lockard, Jon, Publications 1983-1997 (Box 20)
    - Locke, Rovan 1977 (Box 20)
    - McLoyd, Vonnie 1987 (Box 20)
    - McLoyd, Vonnie, Publications 1979-1983, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Makoni, Sinfree 2000 (Box 20)
    - Mitchell, Michele 2004 (Box 20)
    - Moody, Charles 1992 (Box 20)
    - Morris, Aldon 1981-1986 (Box 20)
    - Norman, Martha 1989 (Box 20)
    - Owusu, Maxwell 1978-1996 (Box 20)
    - Patton, Sharon 1983-1993 (Box 20)
    - Patton, Sharon, Publications 1983-1992 (Box 20)
    - Porter, Cornelia 1991 (Box 20)
    - Quarcoopome, Nii 1990-1993 (Box 20)
    - Ransby, Barbara 1988-1989 (Box 20)
    - Ransby, Barbara, Publications 1987-1990 (Box 20)
    - Richard, Glen 1991 (Box 20)
    - Roberts, Allen 1982-1988 (Box 20)
    - Roberts, Allen, Publications 1979-1986, 5 folders (Box 20)
    - Roberts, Allen, Refrigerator Project, Mr. Wizard 1983-1984 (Box 20)
      (includes photo)
    - Ross, Richard, Publications, undated. (Box 20)
    - Samoff, Joel, Publications 1979 (Box 20)
    - Scott, Rebecca 1986-1991 (Box 20)
    - Shepherd, Verne, Publications 1991 (Box 20)
    - Shirley, George 1988-1989 (Box 20)
    - Standifer, James 1985-2000 (Box 20)
    - Stone, Pauline 1979-1982 (Box 20)
    - Stone, Pauline, Publications 1975-1980, 1 folders (Box 20)
      (1 of 5 folders)
    - Stone, Pauline, Publications 1975-1980, 4 folders (Box 21)
      (2-5 of 5 folders)
    - Sudarkasa, Niara 1981-1992 (Box 21)
    - Sudarkasa, Niara, Publications 1963-1987, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Theoharis, Jeanne undated (Box 21)
    - Tillery, Alvin 2004 (Box 21)
    - Twumasi, Yaw undated (Box 21)
    - Ukadike, Nwachukwu Frank 1990-1992 (Box 21)
    - Ukadike, Nwachukwu Frank, Publications 1988-1994 (Box 21)
    - Uzoigwe, Godfrey 1981 (Box 21)
    - Uzoigwe, Godfrey, Publications 1971-1988, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Wagaw, Teshome 1981-1999 (Box 21)
    - Wagaw, Teshome, Publications, 1971-1991, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Walton, Hanes 1990 (Box 21)
    - Whatley, Warren 1983-1996 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Ernest 1984-1989 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Francille undated (Box 21)
    - Woods, Ronald 1980-1982 (Box 21)
    - Young, Alford 1998 (Box 21)
    - Zafar, Rafia (Box 21)
    - Associates 1971-1993 (Box 21)
    - Directories 1977-2004 (Box 21)
    - Exchange Programs, Benin 1981-1987 (Box 21)
    - Exchange Programs, South Africa 1991 (Box 21)
    - Leave and Space 1983-1985 (Box 22)
    - Research and Teaching Assistants 1991-1994 (Box 22)
    - Research Seminars 1993-1994 (Box 22)
    - Searches 1987-1993 (Box 22)
  - Persons, non-faculty 1986-2001
    - Staff 1988-1989 (Box 22)
    - Visiting Scholars
      - Non-Parks-King Chavez 1986-1990 (Box 22)
      - Parks-King-Chavez Program 1990-1994 (Box 22)
      - Moody Scholars, Zhuwau, Thomas 2001 (Box 22)
  - Programs and events 1972-2002
    - Chronological files 1972-2004, 10 folders (Box 22)
    - Black History Month 1978-2002 (Box 22)
    - Black History Month, Rosa Parks and Kwame Toure 1983 (Box 22)
    - Christmas Celebrations 1987-1993 (Box 22)
    - College Day 1987-1988 (Box 22)
    - Film Series 1992-1993 (Box 22)
    - Graduate Receptions 2001-2002 (Box 22)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., Commemorations 1990-1995, 2002, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Open House 1983, 1990-1994 (Box 22)
    - Post-Doctoral, DuBois-Mandela-Rodney Fellowship 1988-1995 (Box 22)
    - Workshops 1991-2000
      - Inventions of Africa 1991-1992 (Box 22)
      - New Nations and New Relations in the Post-Cold War World 1994 (Box 22)
      - African Workshop 1998 (Box 22)
      - Material Processes: Textiles and Texts in the African Diaspora 2000 (Box 22)
  - Publications 1971-2000
    - Brochures 1975-2000 (Box 22)
    - CAAS News 1993 (Box 22)
    - Black Faculty and Staff Directories 1974-1983, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Discussion Papers, Black Educational Achievement Over the Life-Course 1988, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Guide to Procedures and Services 1989-1993 (Box 22)
    - Monograph and Report Series 1971 (Box 22)
    - News and Notes 1988, 2001-2003 (Box 22)
    - Newsletters, Series 01 and 02 1970, 1973 (Box 22)
    - Newsletters, Series 03 ("Ozi Oma") 1973 (Box 22)
    - Newsletters, Series 04 1974-1975 (Box 22)
    - Newsletters, Series 05 1984-1990, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Newsletters, The Tide, volume one 1971 (Box 22)
      (1 of 2 folders)
    - Newsletters, The Tide, volume one 1971 (Box 23)
      (2 of 2 folders)
    - Reviews of CAAS Publications 1986 (Box 23)
    - South Africa Initiatives Office (SAIO) Update 2000 (Box 23)
    - Voices of the African Diaspora 1990-1994 (Box 23)
  - Research projects 1982-1997
    - Chikwaka Rural Hospital, Zimbabwe 1983 (Box 23)
    - Contemporary History Project Undated (Box 23)
    - Detroit Politics Bibliographic Project 1988-1990 (Box 23)
    - Ford Foundation Project;1990-1997, 8 folders (Box 23)
    - Ford Foundation Project: Michael Naylor Proposal re: Oakland University 1991 (Box 23)
    - Gender and Campus Race Differences in Black Student Performance 1986, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Immigration and Black Ethnicity in the United States 1983 (Box 23)
    - National Study of Black College Students 1982-1986 (Box 23)
    - Parks-King-Chavez Fellowship Mini-Course, Correspondence 1987-1989 (Box 23)
    - Parks-King-Chavez Fellowship Mini-Course, Guest Speakers 1987-1988 (Box 23)
    - Post-Emancipation Societies Project 1985-1992 (Box 23)
    - Program for Research on Black Americans 1984 (Box 23)
    - Robert Hayden Film Archive 1990 (Box 23)
    - Rockefeller Foundation 1992-1997 (Box 23)
    - Separate and Unequal The Racial Divide (Detroit) 1989 (Box 24)
    - Update on Student Retention 1989 (Box 24)
  - Rodney, Walter, Student Essay Competition 1985-1997
    - General 1985-1997 (Box 24)
  - Study abroad 1986-2005
    - Caribbean 1989, 3 folders (Box 24)
      (Transcripts of lectures by Kathleen Drayton, Ricky Singh, Aggrey Brown, George Lamming, Stanley Greaves)
    - Jamaica 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - South Africa 2002, 2005 (Box 24)
    - West Africa, Benin 1986-1988 (Box 24)
    - West Africa, Ghana 2002, 2005 (Box 24)
    - West Africa, Ghana, Student Letters from 1970, 1999 (Box 24)
  - Working papers 1990-1998
    (Some papers are related to the First Annual Graduate Student Multidisciplinary Conference (1991), others to "Remapping of Scholarship: African Peoples in the Industrial Age," CAAS colloquia, and student essay prizes.)
    - 22. Siba N. Grovogui 1990 (Box 24)
    - 23. Guyora Binder 1990 (Box 24)
    - 24. Mary Alice Parker 1991 (Box 24)
    - 25. Thomas Holt 1991 (Box 24)
    - 26. Nancy Davis Corley 1991 (Box 25)
    - 27. Angela Winand 1991 (Box 25)
    - 28. Otto Gonzalez,1991 (Box 25)
    - 29. Nancy Racquel Mirabel 1991 (Box 25)
    - 30. Tracye Matthews 1991 (Box 25)
    - 31. Kyra Gaunt 1991 (Box 25)
    - 32. Timothy D. Taylor 1991 (Box 25)
    - 33. Bilinda Straight 1991 (Box 25)
    - 34. Todd C. Shaw 1991 (Box 25)
    - 42. Robin D. G. Kelley 1992 (Box 25)
    - 44. Uzo Esonwanne 1992 (Box 25)
    - 47. Babacar Fall 1993 (Box 25)
    - 50. Sylvia Wynter 1994 (Box 25)
    - 52. Nahum D. Chandler 1994 (Box 25)
    - 53. Antonio Sergio Alfredo Guimaraes 1994 (Box 25)
    - 54. Denise A. Herd 1994 (Box 25)
    - 55. Carolyn Cooper 1994 (Box 25)
    - 56. Abiola Irele 1994 (Box 25)
    - 57. Martha Abreu 1994 (Box 25)
    - 58. Antonio Sergio Alfredo Guimaraes 1994 (Box 25)
    - 59. Draft Conference Papers 1994 (Box 25)
    - 60. Tyler Stovall 1994 (Box 25)
    - 61. Joe W. Trotter 1994 (Box 25)
    - 62. Warren Whatley and Gavin Wright 1994 (Box 25)
    - 63. Colloquium Series 1994-1995 (Box 25)
    - 64. Robert W. Slenes 1995 (Box 25)
    - 68. David M. Freund 1995 (Box 25)
    - 77. Earl Lewis and Heidi Ardizzone 1996 (Box 25)
    - 78. Elizabeth Higginbotham 1996 (Box 25)
    - 84. Kwesi Yankah 1996 (Box 25)
    - 88. Matthew Countryman 1997 (Box 25)
    - 89. David Nicholls 1996 (Box 25)
    - 90. Kathleen Malone O'Connor 1997 (Box 25)
    - 93. Jean-Paul Bado 1997 (Box 25)
    - 95. Patsy Lewis 1997 (Box 25)
    - 96. Erin N. Winkler 1997 (Box 25)
    - 97. Patrick B. Hill 1997 (Box 25)
    - 98. Adrian Burgos, Jr. 1997 (Box 25)
    - 99. Mimi Sheller 1997 (Box 25)
    - 101. Bob W. White 1997 (Box 25)
    - 103. Teshome G. Wagaw 1997 (Box 25)
    - 108. Danielle R. Washington 1998 (Box 25)
    - 109. Gail J. Drakes 1998 (Box 25)
    - African Peoples in the Industrial Age, David G. Nicholls, Jeanne F. Theoharis, Amy Jordan-Rahman 1996 (Box 25)
    - African Peoples in the Industrial Age, Kate Masur, Hajj Malik Womack 1996 (Box 25)
    - Colloquium Series, Heather Ann Thompson, Brian Meeks, Maria Helena P.T. Machado 1996-1997 (Box 25)
    - Colloquium Series, P. Jane Splawn, Rafia Zafar, Dieudonné-Christophe Mbala Nkanga 1997-1998 (Box 25)
    - Constructions of Manhood and Womanhood, Michael Awkward, Waldo E. Johnson Jr. 1996 (Box 25)
    - Constructions of Manhood and Womanhood, Elsa Barkley Brown, Marlon B. Ross 1996 (Box 25)
    - Exploring the Dimensions of Life, Timothy Burke, Samuel Martinez, Nwachukwu Frank Ukadike 1993-1994 (Box 25)
    - Exploring the Dimensions of Life, Sidney Chalhoub, Nantang Jua 1995 (Box 25)
    - Exploring the Dimensions of Life, Matthew J. Countryman, Heinz Klug, Donna D. Daniels 1995-1996 (Box 25)
    - Historical Perspectives, Jonathan Simon, Thomas C. Holt, Sidney Chalhoub, Verene A. Shepherd 1991-1992 (Box 25)
    - New Nations and New Relations, Benigna Zimba 1995 (Box 25)
    - Postemancipation Societies, Glen Richards, Frederick Cooper, Ada Ferrer 1991 (Box 25)
    - Postemancipation Societies, Earl Lewis 1991 (Box 25)
    - Transformations of Power and Culture in Africa, Veit Erlmann, Kelly M. Askew, Winifred C. Nweke, Tiyanjana Maluwa 1996 (Box 25)
  - Photographs 1977-1994, undated
    - Art (Box 27)
    - Baker Mandela Center Artwork and Photos undated (Box 27)
    - Black Student Monthly prints and negatives 1992-1994 (Box 27)
    - CAAS 20th Anniversary 1991 (Box 27)
    - CAAS visitors (identified) undated (Box 27)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program Mentoring Program undated (Box 27)
    - Dated negatives 1987, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Dated photo shoot 1985 (Box 27)
    - Dated photos 1990, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Identified people (Box 27)
    - Kwame Ture and Rosa Parks 1983 (Box 27)
    - Lockard murals (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified undated, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Negatives for Lockard and BAM Conference poster (Box 27)
    - Sharyl L. White Photos 1977 (Box 27)
    - South African Initiatives Office 1993 (Box 27)
    - Study Abroad Jamaica photos and slides 1991-1995, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Teshome Wagaw Ethiopian Study undated (Box 27)
    - Women of Color Task Force Career Conferences undated (Box 27)
    - Zeta Phi Beta Sorority undated (Box 27)
  - Posters
    - 8 posters and one certificate (Folder FimuC26)
- Audio recordings on cassettes 1975-2001
  The series "Audio recordings on cassettes" contains 486 cassettes, and largely consists of spoken word recordings of talks and professional meetings. Many of these cassettes have been digitized. The quality of these recordings is uneven -- some are very good, and others were made with portable recording equipment by volunteers. Because of uncertainty about the copyright status of these recordings, the digitized files are available for use in the reading room only.
  The cassettes are divided into seventeen subseries, arranged chronologically unless otherwise indicated: Early recorded speakers, tapes 1-76, 1975-1984 (arranged alphabetically by speaker's name); Jamaica Study Abroad Program, tapes 77-109, 1991 (arranged by tape number designated by CAAS); Gender and Urban Poverty Conference, tapes 110-116, 1996; Brown bag talks, tapes 117-202, 1986-1995; Dialogue series, tapes 203-221, 1991-1993; Robert Hayden Memorial, tapes 222-235, 1990, Workshop on Strengthening CAAS and Africana Studies at U-M, tapes 236-243, 1989, CAAS Symposium for Black History Month: Black American Families, tapes 244-253, 1991, Inventions of Africa: Africa in the Literatures of the Continent and the Diaspora Workshops, tapes 254-258, 1991-1992, CAAS 20th Anniversary, tapes 259-271, 1991, Race, Culture and the Politics of Intellectual Inquiry Lecture Series, tapes 272-278, 1991-1992, Remapping of Scholarship: African peoples in the Industrial Age, tapes, tapes 279-284, 1994, Graduate Student Conference [became Student of Color of Rackham (SCOR), tapes 285-293, 1991-1993, Barbados, tapes 310-330, 1989, Martin Luther King (MLK) Day, tapes 331-350, 1987-1992, CAAS Mini-course 324: Black Educational Achievement over the Life-Course, tapes 351-361, 1988, and Chronological events, tapes 352-486, 1983-2001. The last named subseries, Chronological events is the largest, comprising 137 recordings. Undated tapes appear at the end of this subseries.
  - Early Recorded Speakers
    - James Banks: World of a Black Child 1975-06-26, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-1-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-1-2
    - James Chaffers: Architecture as Special Responsibility 1977-11-22, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-2-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-2-2
    - Jonas Chenault and Ozzie Edwards: World of Black Child 1975-06-25, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-3-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-3-2
    - Chinweizu: The Assault on Industrial Systems on Global Ecology 1980-10-23, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-4-1
    - John Henrik Clarke: Walter Rodney and the Black Radical Tradition: An Historical Perspective. First Annual Walter Rodney Memorial Lecture (lecture part of Black History Month) 1982-03-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-5-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-5-2
    - Ron Daniels: Revitalizing Independent Black Politics: Towards a Strategy for the 1980’s 1978-06-12, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-6-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-6-2
    - Diggs Lecture: Black History Panel Part1 1978-02-13, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-7-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-7-2
    - Diggs Lecture: Black History Panel Part 2 1978-02-13, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-8-1
    - Isawa Elaigwu: The Barracks and the Ballot Box 1979-04-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-9-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-9-2
    - Edgar Epps: School Desegregation, Self-Perception and Achievement, Orientation of Minority Children undated, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-10-1
    - W. Reynolds Farley: Catching up? Recent Trends in the Social and Economic Status of Blacks 1983-03-02, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-11-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-11-2
    - Samuel Gardner: The Justice System and How it Affects Blacks 1978-02-15, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-12-1 (Box 28)
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-12-2
    - George Goodman: Black Students at U of M in the 1970’s 1980-02-13, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-13-1 (Box 28)
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-13-2
    - George Goodman: Black Students at U of M in the 1970’sf 1980-02-13, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-14-1 (Box 28)
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-14-2
    - Bryant Bunyon Goodman and Janice O'Neal: The National Presidential Elections 1980: The Day After 1980-11-01, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-15-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-15-2
    - David Gordon: Black African States and the Struggle for Southern Africa 1979-02-14, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-16-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-16-2
    - David F. Gordon: Reagan & Africa: What are the prospects? 1981-04-01, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-17-1
    - Obika Gray: State Power and Formats of Opposition: Post Independence Jamaica, 1962-1974 1980-12-10, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-18-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-18-2
    - John L. Gwaltney: Core Black Culture 1982-11-22, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-20-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-20-2
    - Michael Harper: The Modality of Black American Poetry 1977-10-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-21-1
    - Robert B. Hill: The Black Family in Transition Winter 1984, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-23-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-23-2
    - James Horton: The World of the Black Child 1975-06-24, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-25-1
    - Murray Jackson: The Politics of Urban Higher Education” (CAAS Colloquium) 1980-09-24, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-26-1
    - Eva Jessye: Black Music From My Experience: Roots, Church, and Elsewhere 1978-05-17, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-27-1
    - Marcus Jones: The Epistemological Vacuum in Black Critiques of Contemporary Social Science 1977-11-29, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-28-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-28-2
    - Nolan Jones: Questions Concerning the Coming Crisis for Black America 1978-02-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-29-1
    - Jemadari Kamara: China and the Struggles of African Peoples 1978-10-18, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-30-1
      - [side 1] new, 2012140-SR-30-2
    - Jemadari Kamara: The Challenge of BAM for the 1980s” (Jemadari Kamara, Ben Newhouse, Vicky Rowels, Virna Hobbs, Janice O’Neal, Obika Gray) 1980-03-20, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-31-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-31-2
    - Charles Kidd: UM a Decade After BAM 1980-03-19, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-32-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-32-2
    - Frederick Lee: Black and White Political Attitudes Towards the Presidency 1978-03-29, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-33-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-33-2
    - Howard Lindsay: Internal Colonialism: The City of Detroit, a Cube? 1980-02-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-34-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-34-2
    - Jon Onye Lockard: Afro-Brazilian Relationships with African and Afro-American Art 1978-10-25, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-35-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-35-2
    - Jon Onye Lockard: African Retentions in Suriname and Brazil: Arts, Cultures, and Religions 1983-02-16, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-36-1
    - Rovan Locke: Nigerian Politics After the Elections: Decivilianization undated, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-37-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-37-2
    - Glenn Loury: The Economic Prospects for Blacks in the 1980s 1980-01-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-38-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-38-2
    - Ali Mazrui: Black America and the Legacy of Jomo Kenyatta 1978-09-27, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-39-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-39-2
    - Charles Moody, Gwen Baker, James Banks: Education of Black Children 1975-06-26, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-40-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-40-2
    - Aldon Morris: The Rise of the Black Southern Sit-In Movement of 1960 1980-10-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-41-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-41-2
    - Nizar Motani: British Imperialism at Work in East Africa: The Case of the Civil Service 1979-11-28, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-42-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-42-2
    - Never a Man 1982-03-10, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-43-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-43-2
    - Benjamin Newhouse, Cynthia Hardy: Towards a Network of Black Professional Organizations 1980-12-03, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-44-1
    - Jonathan Ngate: The African Landscape: The City and the Village in the Novels of Achebe and Laye 1981-03-11, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-45-1
    - Jonathan Ngate: The African Landscape: The City and the Village in the Novels of Achebe and Laye undated, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-46-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-46-2
    - Jonathan Ngate: A Tentative Workable Definition of Third World Literature 1984-03-16, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-47-1
    - Levi Nwachuku: African States and the Challenge of Independence 1978-11-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-48-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-48-2
    - Michael Olisa: Africa: New Dimensions of Dependency 1979-02-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-49-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-49-2
    - Ike Oyeka, Richard Bradley: Lessons from the Role of Science and Technology in Ancient Africa 1979-03-28, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-50-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-50-2
    - Lorraine Perry and Madison Foster: Black Self-Satisfaction 1977-12-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-51-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-51-2
    - Dorothy Porter: Fifty Years of Collecting 1981-03-12, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-52-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-52-2
    - Christopher Roberts: Diagnosis and Divination Among the Tabwe of Zaire 1980-11-19, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-53-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-53-2
    - Cedric Robinson: Richard Wright as a Marxist Theorist 1978-11-15, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-54-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-54-2
    - Randall Robinson: Black Americans and the Struggle for Southern Africa in the 80s 1980-01-30, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-55-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-55-2
    - Joel Samoff: Ujamaa: Poverty and Socialism in Tanzania 1978-11-01, audiocassette (Box 28)